Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Labor Movement Serials WAG.345
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Labor unions and organizations, 1890-2012; 72.1 Linear Feet in 19 record cartons, 29 manuscript boxes, 2 half manuscript boxes, and 152 flat boxes
  - Subseries I.I: Labor Coalitions and Organizations, 1890-2012; 19.8 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 16 manuscript boxes, and 38 flat boxes
    - Strike Back: Trenton Area United Workers, Trenton, NJ, 1971; cuid10784 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Tracing a Transformation in Industrial Relations: U.S. Department of Labor Bureau of Labor-Management Relations and Cooperative Programs, Washington, DC, 1988 (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - U.S. Labor Law and the Future of Labor-Management Cooperation: U.S. Department of Labor Bureau of Labor-Management Relations and Cooperative Programs, Washington, DC, 1988 (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - Boletin Mensual: Union General de Trabajadores, 1950-1951; cuid10785 (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Union Label Trades News and Directory: Union Label Trades Department of the State of New York/Union Label League & Central Body Label Committees of the State of New York, New York, NY, 1951; cuid10786 (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Racine Labor: Union Labor Publishing Company Inc., Racine, WI, 1992-1995; cuid10787 (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Unionist: Unionist, Austin, MN, 1986; cuid10788 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Cornell Union Scribbler: United Auto Workers - Local 188 - Students of Professor Harry Kelber, Ithaca, NY, 1966; cuid10789 (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Build the Nationwide Unemployed League: United Front Committee to Build the Nationwide Unemployed League, New York, NY, 1975; cuid10790 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - U.I.W. 424 News: United Industry Workers 425, Bohemia, NY, 1989; cuid10791 (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Review and Outlook: United Labor-Management Press, New York, NY, 1961; cuid10792 (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Songs for May Day: United May Day Committee, New York, NY, 1946; cuid10793 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Newsletter: United MayDay Committee, 1975; cuid10794 (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - District 50 News: United Mine Workers of America, Washington, DC, 1946; cuid10795 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Chemical Worker: United Mine Workers of America - District 50, Local #12165, Drug, Chemical and Cosmetic Division, 1940; cuid10796 (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - Coal Miners and the Economy: A UMWA Research Report: United Mine Workers of America - Research Department, Washington, DC, 1974; cuid10797 (Box 143, Folder 15)
    - Memo: United Office and Professional Workers of America - Local 16, New York, NY, 1943; cuid10798 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Packinghouse Workers Champion: United Packinghouse Workers of America - District One, Chicago, IL, 1944; cuid10799 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Public Record: United Public Workers of America, New York, NY, 1950, 1952; cuid10800 (Box 156, Folder 6, Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Our Newspaper: United Workers Association, 1976; cuid10801 (Box 143, Folder 16)
    - Newark Airport Cab Driver's Bulletin: Unity and Struggle, Newark, NJ, 1974; cuid10802 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - University of Illinois bulletin: University of Illinois, Urbana, IL, 1961, 1967; cuid10803 (Box 143, Folder 17)
    - CONET: University of Minnesota, 1991; cuid10804 (Box 143, Folder 18)
    - Trenton Rank & File: UTF, Trenton, NJ, 1972; cuid10805 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Vermont Labor Reporter: Vermont Labor Council, AFL-CIO, Bellows Falls, VT, 1968, 1975; cuid10806 (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Bulletin: Washington State Nursing Home Resident Council, Seattle, WA, 1982-1983; cuid10807 (Box 172, Folder 23)
    - The NATCA Voice: The Great Lakes Regional NATCA Newsletter: West End Press, Chicago, IL, 1995; cuid10808 (Box 172, Folder 21)
    - West Virginia Mine Workers Campaign Bulletin: West Virginia Mine Workers, Charleston, WV, 1931; cuid10809 (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Westchester 60 Plus: Westchester County Office for the Aging, White Plains, NY, 1992; cuid10810 (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - What's Left: Western Massachusetts Labor/Community Support Network, Northampton, MA, 1982; cuid10811 (Box 143, Folder 19)
    - Abestos Update: White Lung Asbestos Information Center, New York, NY, 1995-1998; cuid10812 (Box 143, Folder 20)
    - Wildfire: Wildfire, Chicago, IL, 1975-1976; cuid10813 (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Philadelphia Worker: Worker, Philadelphia, Pa, 1975; cuid10814 (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Rochester Worker: Worker, Rochester, NY, 1974; cuid10815 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Subways are for sitting: Worker, circa 1960s; cuid10816 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - A Call to Organize: Worker's Action Comm., Elmhurst, IL, 1970; cuid10817 (Box 143, Folder 21)
    - Workers Action/Obreros en Acción: Workers Action Movement, Chicago, IL, 1974; cuid10818 (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - NYU Workers' Voice: Workers at New York University, New York, NY, 1972; cuid10819 (Box 172, Folder 19)
    - Workers Defense Bulletin: Workers Defense League, New York, NY, 1947-1949; cuid10820 (Box 143, Folder 22)
    - Workers Defense League - Anniversary Journal: Workers Defense League, New York, NY, 1972, 1981, 1983; cuid10821 (Box 143, Folder 23)
    - Last-Minute News: Workers Defense League - National Office, New York, NY, circa 1940; cuid10822 (Box 143, Folder 24)
    - Workers Democracy: Workers' Democracy Network, Trenton, NJ, 2003; cuid10823 (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - New World: Workers Press, New York, N.Y., 2008-2009; cuid10824 (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - Democratizing the Workplace - Ideas Examples and Suggestions on Democratizing the Workplace from Job Enrichment to Worker Control: Workers' Self-Management Group, AFSC, Cambridge, MA, circa 1970; cuid10825 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Working Families News: Working Families, Brooklyn, NY, 2000; cuid10826 (Box 143, Folder 25)
    - Southerner: Dalton, GA, 1955; cuid10827 (Box 156, Folder 17)
  - Subseries I.J: Public Employees, 1921-2007; 9.2 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 6 manuscript boxes, and 13 flat boxes
    This series collects various uncataloged serials and newsletters mainly issued by large national organizations including the American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees; Civil Service Employees Association; Civil Service Employees Association; District Council 1707 Shop Stewards; New York State Department of Labor; and New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University. Weekly and monthly newsletters document union advocacy at a national scale, providing significant coverage of changes in labor law -- collective bargaining; retiree rights; strike actions -- as well as documenting the day-to-day circumstances of particular unions, for example the election of union representatives, and divisions between organizations and rank and file groups.
    - Princeton University Annual Giving: AG Staff at Princeton University, Princeton, NJ, 1968; cuid10828 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Contract Now!: American Federation of School Administrators (AFL-CIO) - Local 1, 1998; cuid10829 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Voice of 1707: American Federation of State, County & Municipal Employees, New York, NY, 1974; cuid10830 (Box 74, Folder 3, Box 79, Folder 1-5, Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Union News-Views: American Federation of State, County & Municipal Employees - Council 16, Middletown, CT, 1967; cuid10831 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Boycott Shell Bulletin: American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Washington, DC, 1989; cuid10832 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Weekly Report: American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Washington, DC, 2002; cuid10833 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - AFSCME/New York State: American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFL-CIO), Albany, NY, 1975; cuid10834 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Collective Bargaining Reporter: American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFL-CIO), Washington, DC, 1996-1997; cuid10835 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Retiree Rights: American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFL-CIO), Washington, DC, 1993; cuid10836 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Spotlight: American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1953, 1956-1959; cuid10837 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Women's Letter: American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFL-CIO), Washington, DC, 1981; cuid10838 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Legislative Action: American Labor Party, New York, NY, 1947; cuid10839 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - News: American Labor Party, New York, NY, circa 1950s; cuid10840 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Record: American Labor Party of New York State, New York, NY, 1948; cuid10841 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - New York Citizen: American Labor Party of NY County, New York, NY, 1939; cuid10842 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Voices in Politics: American Postal Workers, Washington, DC, 1997 (Box 193, Folder 11)
    - Arizona Professor: Arizona College and University Faculty Association, Phoenix, AZ, 1971; cuid10843 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Bulletin!: Associated Industries of New York State, Inc., Albany, NY, 1977; cuid10844 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Legislative News Letter: ASU-New York District, New York, NY, 1939; cuid10845 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Guidelines for AFT Involvement in Big City School Integration: Big City Locals of the American Federation of Teachers in Conference, Chicago, IL, 1963; cuid10846 (Box 172, Folder 33)
    - Sendout: Brooklyn Union Gas Employees, Brooklyn, NY, 1973; cuid10847 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Telephone Workers' News: Brotherhood of Utility Employees of America, New York, NY, 1936; cuid10848 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Service Union Reporter: California State Council of Service Employees (AFL-CIO), Los Angeles, CA, circa 1960s; cuid10849 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - California Pride: California State Employees Association, Sacramento, CA, 1989; cuid10850 (Box 74, Folder 18-21)
    - Labor Times: Chicago and Central States Joint Board, Chicago, IL, 1987; cuid10851 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Moving Forward: Chinese Staff and Workers' Association - Youth Group, New York, NY, 1993; cuid10852 (Box 74, Folder 22)
    - State of Our Union - CSEA 2006/2005 Legislative Summary: Civil Service Employees Association, New York, NY, cuid10853 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Essentially Women: Civil Service Employees Association, Inc. / Local 1000, Albany, NY, 1996-1998; cuid10854 (Box 74, Folder 23)
    - Public Sector: Civil Service Employees Association, Local 1000 (American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees), Albany, NY, 1990-1996; cuid10855 (Box 82, Folder 1-5, Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Civil Service Standard: Civil Service Standard, Inc., New York, NY, 1938; cuid10856 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Guild-Gram: Civil Service Technical Guild - Local 375, DC 37, New York, NY, 1990; cuid10857 (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - Committee for Real Change in DC 37 (CRC): Committee for Real Change, District Council 37, Brooklyn, NY, 1999; cuid10858 (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Rank and File Caucus Union News: Committee of Concerned State Workers, New York, NY, 1979; cuid10859 (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - CPSR Newsletter: Computer Professionals for Social Responsibility, Palo Alto, CA, 1990; cuid10860 (Box 74, Folder 27)
    - CSA Change: Council of Supervisors and Administrators of the City of New York, New York, NY, 1991-1994 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - DC 1707 Street Heat: DC 1707 AFSCME, 2000; cuid10861 (Box 74, Folder 28)
    - Voice: DC 1707 AFSCME, 1978, 1983, 1986-2005; cuid10862 (Box 77, Folder 1-5)
    - Union Women United: DC 37, Women's Committee, New York, NY, 1983; cuid10863 (Box 74, Folder 29)
    - How to Stop Sexual Harassment: DC 37's National Union (AFSCME), New York, NY, 1993; cuid10864 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Home Care Concerns: District Council 1707 - Local 389 and the Home Care Employees Health and Welfare Fund, New York, NY, 1993-1996; cuid10865 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Steward Leader: District Council 1707 Shop Stewards (American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees), New York, NY, 1996; cuid10866 (Box 74, Folder 30)
    - Local 1930 Newsline: District Council 37 (AFSCME, AFL-CIO) - New York Public Library Guild, New York, NY, 1987-1989; cuid10867 (Box 74, Folder 31)
    - Contract News: District Council 37 Locals 371, 420, 1549, circa 1970s; cuid10868 (Box 74, Folder 32)
    - Minority Affairs: Division of Minority Affairs, Washington State University, Pullman, WA, 1988; cuid10869 (Box 74, Folder 33)
    - Education WOB: workers organizing bulletin: Education Workers Industrial Union 620, Cortland, NY, 1994; cuid10870 (Box 74, Folder 34)
    - Public Service Reporter: Federation of State Employees, Washington, DC, 1994 (Box 180, Folder 22)
    - FUSA Advocate: Florida United Service Association, Jacksonville, FL, 1974; cuid10871 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Local 200 Reporter: General Service Employees Union (AFL-CIO) - Local 200, Syracuse, NY, 1978; cuid10872 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - GCEOC - CIO News: Government and Civic Employees Organizing Committee, CIO, New York, NY, 1953; cuid10873 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Voice of the Grand Council of Columbia Associations in Civil Service: Grand Council of Columbia Associations in Civil Service, New York, NY, 1965; cuid10874 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Illinois Labor: Illinois State Industrial Union Council, Chicago, IL, 1954; cuid10875 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - ISEA News: Indiana State Employees Association (ISEA), Indianapolis, IN, 1983-1987; cuid10876 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Legislative News/Legislative Newsbrief: Indiana State Employees Association (ISEA), Indianapolis, IN, 1984; cuid10877 (Box 74, Folder 35)
    - Newsbrief: Indiana State Employees Association (ISEA), Indianapolis, IN, 1983; cuid10878 (Box 74, Folder 36)
    - Sentinel: Indiana State Employees Association (ISEA), 1988-1989; cuid10879 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - News & Views: Institute for Food and Development Policy, Oakland, CA, 1994; cuid10880 (Box 74, Folder 37)
    - ISR Journal: Institute for Staff Relations and Governance at New York University, 1969; cuid10881 (Box 74, Folder 38)
    - Illinois Public Employee Relations Report: Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, Champaign, IL, 1989; cuid10882 (Box 74, Folder 39)
    - International Fire Fighter: International Association of Fire Fighters, Washington, DC, 1981-1986; cuid10883 (Box 78, Folder 1-2)
    - Police Chronicle: International Brotherhood of Police Officers, Quincy, MA, 1986-1996; cuid10884 (Box 78, Folder 3-4)
    - Bulletin: International Committee of Municipal Workers and Workers in Public Services, 1934; cuid10885 (Box 74, Folder 40)
    - Public Employees Conference Proceedings: International Foundation of Employee Benefit Plans, San Diego, CA, 1978 (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - Guard News: International Union, United Plant Guard Workers of America (UPGWA), Roseville, MI, 1982; cuid10886 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - IHEA Communique: Iowa Higher Education Association, Des Moines, IA, 1972; cuid10887 (Box 74, Folder 41)
    - Live-Wire: Live Wire, Los Angeles, CA, 1951; cuid10888 (Box 74, Folder 42)
    - New York Connection: Local 131, New York, NY, 1989; cuid10889 (Box 74, Folder 43)
    - Billboard Guildsman: Locked-Out Staff of the Billboard, New York, NY, 1946; cuid10890 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - R.A. Unionist: Lodge 206 AFGE, 1936; cuid10891 (Box 74, Folder 44)
    - Unionist: Lodge 206 AFGE, 1937; cuid10892 (Box 74, Folder 45)
    - Bargaining Update: Massachusetts Society of Professors Faculty Staff Union, 1984; cuid10893 (Box 74, Folder 46)
    - Bulletin: Members United for a Better Contract, A Coalition of Concerned APWU Members, 1981; cuid10894 (Box 74, Folder 47)
    - Local 44 Union News: Metro Tri-State Police Federation of Investigators and Security Trades (IUPA, AFL-CIO), 1982; cuid10895 (Box 74, Folder 48)
    - Michigan CIO News: Michigan State Industrial Council (CIO), Detroit, MI, 1948; cuid10896 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - School of Labor and Industrial Relations Newsletter: Michigan State University, East Lansing, MI, 1990; cuid10897 (Box 74, Folder 49)
    - Viewpoints MSLC: Missouri State Labor Council, Jefferson City, MO, 1986; cuid10898 (Box 74, Folder 50)
    - Amnesty Issue: N.Y. Metro Area Postal Union, 1979; cuid10899 (Box 74, Folder 51)
    - NAGE Reporter: National Association of Government Employees, Washington, DC, 1986-1996, 1999; cuid10900 (Box 80, Folder 2-3)
    - Manhattan Bronx Chapter #23: National Association of Retired Federal Employees, Floral Park, NY, 1989-1992; cuid10901 (Box 74, Folder 52, Box 180, Folder 16)
    - NFA Reports: National Education Association, Washington, DC, 1971-1972; cuid10902 (Box 172, Folder 31)
    - Federation News Service: National Federation of Post Office Clerks, Washington, DC, 1953-1956; cuid10903 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - NFSSE Forum: National Federation of Social Service Employees, New York, NY, 1968; cuid10904 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Mail Handler Exchange: National Postal Mail Handlers Union, Washington, DC, 1988-1989; cuid10905 (Box 74, Folder 53)
    - Local 300 Mail Handler News: National Postal Mail Handlers Union - Local 300 (AFL-CIO-CLC), New York, NY, 1995; cuid10906 (Box 74, Folder 54)
    - New Directions: New Directions Caucus of the UFT, New York, N.Y., 1976, 1979; cuid10907 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Civil Service Leader: New York City Civil Service Retired Employees Association, New York, NY, 1976; cuid10908 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Newsletter: New York City Department of Labor, Division of Labor Research, New York, NY, 1961; cuid10909 (Box 74, Folder 55)
    - Fed's News Flash: New York Federation of Post Office Clerks, New York, NY, 1954; cuid10910 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Universitas: New York State AFT College and University Council, New York, NY, 1968; cuid10911 (Box 74, Folder 56)
    - Labor Alert: New York State Assembly Labor Committee, Albany, NY, 2001; cuid10912 (Box 74, Folder 57)
    - Promises and Performance/Special Bulletin No. 3: New York State CIO, New York, NY, circa 1970s; cuid10913 (Box 74, Folder 58)
    - Weekly News: New York State Council of Senior Citizens, New York, NY, 1995; cuid10914 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Jobs Hot-Line: New York State Department of Labor, Albany, NY, 1977; cuid10915 (Box 74, Folder 59)
    - Occupational Injuries and Illness Survey: New York State Department of Labor, Albany, NY, 1994; cuid10916 (Box 74, Folder 60)
    - Labor Bulletin: New York State Department of Labor - Office of Communication, Albany, NY, 1984, 1986; cuid10917 (Box 74, Folder 61)
    - Labor Research Report: New York State Department of Labor Division of Research and Statistics, Albany, NY, 1988; cuid10918 (Box 74, Folder 62)
    - Labor Organizations in New York State, 1955: New York State Department of Labor, Division of Research and Statistics, Albany, NY, 1956; cuid10919 (Box 74, Folder 63)
    - State Employee News: New York State Employees Council 50, Albany, NY, 1968; cuid10920 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Newsletter: New York State Labor Department, Albany, NY, 1972; cuid10921 (Box 74, Folder 64)
    - Renewing the Community, Celebrating Diversity: New York State Labor-Religion Coalition, Albany, NY, 1995; cuid10922 (Box 74, Folder 65)
    - News-Gram: New York State Legislative and Education Board, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Albany, NY, 1968; cuid10923 (Box 74, Folder 66)
    - Communicator: New York State Public Employees Federation, New York, NY, 1975, 1986-1987, 1995; cuid10924 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - New York State Public Employees Communicator: New York State Public Employees Federation, Elmsford, NY, 1979 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - PERB News: New York State Public Employment Relations Board, Albany, NY, 1968-1978; cuid10925 (Box 172, Folder 34-35)
    - Bulletin: New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 1955; cuid10926 (Box 74, Folder 67)
    - ILR Bulletin: New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 1970; cuid10927 (Box 74, Folder 68)
    - ILR Reprints/ILR Reprint Series: New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, circa 1990s; cuid10928 (Box 75, Folder 37-40)
    - Industrial and labor relations Report Card: New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 1972; cuid10929 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Labor Historians' Bulletin: New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 1955, 1959; cuid10930 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - New York State Service Employee: New York State Service Employees Council (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1977-1979, 1982; cuid10931 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - 34&35 Local: News Committee, 1991; cuid10932 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Non-AC News: Nonacademic Workers of the University of Illinois, Urbana, IL, 1972; cuid10933 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Up From the Shadows: Northern States Co-Operative League, Minneapolis, MN, 1934; cuid10934 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Special Collections: Penn State Special Collections Department, University Park, PA, 1989, 1992-1993; cuid10935 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - On the Line: Police Benevolent Association, New York, NY, 1991-1994; cuid10936 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Detroit Area Postal Action: Postal Action Committee, Detroit, MI, 1976; cuid10937 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - P.O.W. (Post Office Worker): Postal Workers Defense Committee, New York, NY, 1979-1980; cuid10938 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - PSCcuny Newsletter: Professional Staff Conference of the City of New York, New York, NY, 2000; cuid10939 (Box 172, Folder 30)
    - The PSC Position on the CUNY Master Plan: Professional Staff Conference of the City of New York, New York, NY, circa 2000; cuid10940 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - PEF-ODDD Newsletter: Public Employees Federation Office of Disability Determinations Division, New York, NY, 1988; cuid10941 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Open Pouch: Railway Mail Association, New York, NY, 1945, 1948-1958; cuid10942 (Box 81, Folder 2-3)
    - Rank and File Postal Worker: Rank and File Postal Worker, Philadelphia, PA, 1976 (Box 221, Folder 13)
    - Men and Ships: A Pictorial of the Maritime Industry: San Francisco Bay Area District Council No. 2, Maritime Federation of the Pacific Coast / Wobbers, Inc., San Francisco, CA, 1937; cuid10943 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Facts: Social Service Employees Union, New York, NY, 1967; cuid10944 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - SSEU News: Social Service Employees Union, New York, NY, 1965-1969; cuid10945 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Untitled newsletter: Social Service Employees Union - Local 371, New York, NY, circa 1970; cuid10946 (Box 172, Folder 32)
    - Campaigner: Social Service Employees Union - Local 371 Committee for New Leadership, New York, NY, 1973; cuid10947 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Labor Papers on Microfilm: State Historical Society of Wisconsin, Madison, WI, 1965; cuid10948 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Association Advocate: State of Nevada Employees Association, Carson City, NV, 1990-1991; cuid10949 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Directory of Labor Organizations in New York State 1955: State of New York - Department of Labor Division of Research and Statistics, New York, NY, cuid10950 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Industrial Code Bulletin: State of New York Department of Labor, Albany, NY, circa 1930s; cuid10951 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Special Bulletin: State of New York Department of Labor, 1928; cuid10952 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Weekly Legislative Digest: State of New York Department of Labor, New York, NY, 1951, 1954; cuid10953 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Working: State of New York Department of Labor, Albany, NY, 1994; cuid10954 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Employee: State, County and Municipal Workers of America, Washington, DC, 1938; cuid10955 (Box 81, Folder 6)